prettyimpress.com 2013-05-06

# Cycling Jersey, Custom Cycling Jersey, Customer Service - Privacy Notice - Free Shipping

PrettyImpress respects your privacy and takes your online safety seriously. In order to provide you with the best products, efficient customer service, and timely updates, we record a variety of information from your visit to our site. To better protect your privacy, we provide the notice below explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

Information Collection and Use  
PrettyImpress.com will not sell, share, or rent this information to any outside parties, except as outlined in this policy. One goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide an efficient, meaningful, and customized experience. Information collected includes your name, shipping address, e-mail address. We also require you to submit a username and password of your choice for your future access to your account information. To safeguard that your user name and password remain confidential, DO NOT share this information with anyone. 

Registration and Ordering  
During registration, you will be required to provide your contact information, which includes your name, e-mail address, street address. This information is used to provide you with important PrettyImpress.com services such as automated order status updates via e-mail. 

Cookies  
We customize certain Web page content based upon your browser type and other information provided by our cookie. If you choose to reject the cookie, you can still browse our store but will be unable to use the shopping cart to buy merchandise. The PrettyImpress.com shopping cart cannot function without cookies enabled so that the necessary information to process your order is retained. If you disable cookies, PrettyImpress.com will be unable to accept your online order. We will not share any personally identifiable information provided by this cookie with any third party. We will, however, link data stored in cookies to the personally identifiable information you submitted while on our site. This allows us to personalize your shopping experience and discern user preferences to evoke subconscious feelings of familiarity and assurance.  
THIS SITE'S COOKIES DO NOT AND CANNOT INFILTRATE A USER'S HARD DRIVE TO GATHER A USER'S CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION.

Log Files  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information, and we do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties.

Product Reviews.   
You may choose to submit a product review. If you post a review, we will ask for your Account ID. We are not responsible for any personally identifiable information that you choose to submit as part of your review. We believe you can post a helpful review without disclosing any personal information.

Sharing  
We may employ third party companies to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include order fulfillment, package delivery, marketing assistance, postal and e-mail delivery, customer service, data analysis. The third parties we contract for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and may not use it for other purposes.

Shopping  
As our business continues to evolve, we may acquire or sell business units or subsidiaries. Customer information is one of the business assets that would be transferred in these types of transactions. In such a situation, your personally identifiable information would only be used in a manner consistent with our pre-existing Privacy Notice.  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

Children  
PrettyImpress.com does not sell products for purchase by children. Youth-oriented products are sold for purchase by adults only. If you are under the age of 13, you may only use PrettyImpress.com in the presence of a consenting parent or guardian. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information via the Internet from children under the age of 13. PrettyImpress.com is committed to protecting the welfare and privacy of children.

Links  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that PrettyImpress.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website.

Security  
PrettyImpress.com takes precautions to protect its customers' information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.  
Access to all of our users' information is restricted. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information.   
All PrettyImpress.com servers, including web servers and database servers are housed and maintained in secure locations. Access to the database is strictly monitored and protected from outside access. Internet access is restricted and protected by multiple Checkpoint and Cisco firewalls and password protection. The servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secured environment, inside a secured and locked room. All backups are stored and locked in a high-level security room. Only personnel with proper security clearance have access to these restricted areas.   
If you have any questions or concerns about PrettyImpress.com's security practices, you can contact our customer service.

Correction/Updating/Reviewing Personal Information  
Customers may change or review their stored account information such as street address or e-mail address through our website by visiting our Help section. You must have your username and password in order to access your account. In the event you forget both your username and password, please contact our customer service department for assistance.

Handling of Enquiries, General Concerns and Complaints   
If you have enquiries, general concerns, or complaints about these Terms, or about PrettyImpress’s behaviour in relation to these Terms, you undertake:   
\- to communicate our customer service in the first instance:   
\- to PrettyImpress only;   
\- in sufficient detail;   
Through a channel made available by PrettyImpress for that purpose; 

PrettyImpress undertakes:   
\- to provide one or more channels for communications   
\- to promptly provide acknowledgement of the receipt of communications, including the provision of a copy of the communication, the date and time it was registered, and PrettyImpress 's reference-code -for the communication;   
\- to promptly provide a response to the communication, in an appropriate and meaningful manner.   
You further undertake to not pursue PrettyImpress through any Regulator or the media:   
\- until and unless PrettyImpress has had a reasonable opportunity to respond to the initial communication; and   
\- while PrettyImpress and you remain are conducting a meaningful dialogue about the matter. 

Back to Customer Service
